Kasia Skrzypek

UX/UI Designer

Relevant work experience

GetYourGuide | Feb 2017 - Jul 2021

Brand Imagery Manager

- Acting as the key liaison for brand imagery to support brand awareness and ensure brand consistency across all touchpoints.
- Setting up and documenting visual brand guidelines.
- Adaptation and implementation of a digital visual asset management tool.
- Designing labelling system and workflows for the asset management tool - based on stakeholder needs.
- Responsible for all visual input within the organisation, ensuring it is consistently on brand across a range of online and offline channels.

Wayfair | 2016

Photo editor and QA

- Post-production of lifestyle and product photography for commercial and editorial purposes.
- Photo manipulation and consultancy during photoshoots.
- Digital asset management in accordance with existing guidelines.

Airbnb | 2012-2020

Photographer

- Reaching out to leads.
- Setting up, planning and executing photoshoots of customer apartments in accordance with company brand guidelines.
- Content management and post-production.

Arvato | 2013-2016

Senior Tech Support Specialist for Canon

- B2C support and QA inbound calls and e-mail.
- Photo-Video Mentor for all Northern European teams.
- Manager of the Canon product library setting up equipment maintenance and renting processes.

Education

Career Foundry
Dec 2021 - Present

Frontend for Designers Specizlization

Career Foundry Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

UI for UX Designers Specialization

Career Foundry Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

UX Designer

UAM, Poznań 2001 - 2006 MA in English Language and Linguistics

Contact

katarzyna.skrzypek@gmail.com +49 176 6060 1792 linkedin.com/in/kasia-skrzypek/

About

Photo editor turned UX/UI designer with experience in e-commerce and degree in languages. Passionate about creating customer-centric design solutions to deadline, on budget and with a smile.

Portfolio

www.behance.net/fotoforge

Technical Skills

Branding /Visual Design Interaction Design Story / Journey Mapping Personas Usability Analysis / Testing Wireframing / Prototyping

Tools

Figma / Sketch
Balsamiq
Miro
Adobe Creative Suite
InVision
Jira / Trello,
Siebel / Salesforce

Languages

English - proficient Polish - mother tongue German - fluent Danish - fluent French - beginner

Interests

Social psychology Neuromarketing Historical costuming Scuba diving Photography and film